(Leonard:)Oh, good.
Do you have any fabric softener?
(Penny:)Yeah, sure.
What, are you washing a crocodile?
(Leonard:)No. The pants that Stephanie got me.
(Penny:)Oh, sweetie, you can't machine wash these.
They'll be ruined.
(Penny:)- You sure?
- Absolutely.
(Leonard:)Oh, no. I wish you'd told me that sooner.
- Are you guys having problems?
- No. Everything's fine.
(Leonard:)- Really?
- Yeah, it's wonderful.
(Leonard:)Okay, maybe this whole
living together happened...
(Leonard:)...kind of suddenly,
but it's fine, it's great.
Okay, Leonard, if you're uncomfortable
with the way things are going...
(Penny:)...you're allowed to say something.
(Leonard:)Are you sure? That doesn't sound right.
(Penny:)Believe me, your feelings
are just as important as hers.